UNITE Photographs 6000 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- List of JPS Plants (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Current JPS Photos (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Thompson Comm. In R.R. (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Indianapolis Rally 10/1977 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Pierre Demo. 11/28/1977; NY Board of Trade - Jos. Finley (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Central States Jt. Board of Michigan (Box 32, Folder 14)
- LA Boycotts - Mayor Bradley (Box 32, Folder 15)
- CLUW "Candlelight Rally" JPS 12/8/1977 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Phila. City Hall Display (Box 32, Folder 17)
- 1975 RR Rally (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Unused pix of events covered in SJ (Box 32, Folder 19)
- UNITE Photograph Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  January 97 to June 97
- UNITE Photograph Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  January 98 to June 98
- UNITE Photograph Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  July 98 to Oct. 98
- Versatec (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Veto Override Demos (Box 34, Folder 2)
  39 photographs
- Vita Shoe Company (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Wallace, Earlie Mae Demos-Etc. (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Washington (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Waveline Inc. (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Waynesboro Knitting Mills (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Wellman Industries, Johnsonville, S.C. (Local 2398) (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Winnipeg Story LU 12/1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Jt. Council/Garment Mfg. Assoc. of Western Canada (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Winston Uniform Corp. (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Jack Winter (Milwaukee) (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Women's Rights Demo 1992 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Wonderknit (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Woonsocket (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Work wear (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Workers Bill of Rights Demonstration (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Workers' Memorial Day 1989 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Workers' Memorial Day 1990 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Workers' Memorial Day 1991 NY/Toronto (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Workers Memorial Day 1993 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Workers Memorial Day 1992 - NY (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Working for your life (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Misc. Union Photos (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Picketing of JP Stevens (Box 34, Folder 25)
- JP Stevens - Stockholders meeting (Box 34, Folder 26)
- JPS Pix (Geni) (Box 34, Folder 27)
- JP Stevens - Wallace, NC (Box 34, Folder 28)
- JP Stevens (Box 34, Folder 29)
- JP Stevens - New Contract at 9 plants (Box 34, Folder 30)
- American Labor comes to Yale -- 2003 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- J.P. Stevens - Drakes Branch, Va. (Box 34, Folder 32)
- JP Stevens (Montgomery) (Box 34, Folder 33)
- JP Stevens (New Milford, Conn.) (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Another Stevens Tragedy (Story) (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Women working at JP Stevens (Box 34, Folder 36)
- JP Stevens - Great Falls, NC 1979 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- JP Stevens (Tower?) (Box 34, Folder 38)
- Knoxville Leafleting; Atlanta Leafleting (Box 34, Folder 39)
- Birmingham Leafleting -- 1/28/1977 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Chicago Leafleting (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Philadelphia Luncheon (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Princeton Rally (Box 34, Folder 43)
- Manning Brown Demo (Box 35, Folder 1)
  9 photographs -- not sure on title, handwriting was difficult to read
- Boyd Leedom (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Daris Barber - Back Pay; Helen Newsom - Back Pay (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Cincinnati Leafleting (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Ratification Meeting - 1/1998 Registration (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Ratification Meeting - 1/1998 -- Six District Group Shots (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Ratification Meeting -- 1/1998 Questions from the floor (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Ratification Meeting -- 1/1998 Group Shots (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Ratification Meeting -- 1/1998 Speakers (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Ratification Meeting -- 1/1998 Reception (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 35, Folder 11)
  42 photographs
- Unity House historical marker 2006 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  50 photographs
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Unite House Historical Marker 2006 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 35, Folder 15)
- ILGWU "Historical"; UNITE "Modern" (Box 35, Folder 16)
  3 photographs; 21 slides
- UNITE Demonstrations & Employees (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Triangle Fire - 2002 Commemoration (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous - pulled from other boxes due to size (Box 36, Folder 1)
- UNITE Photographs; Union Health Center (Box 36, Folder 2)
  pulled from graphics folder -- 4 photographs
- UNITE - Sweatshops (Box 36, Folder 3)
- UNITE Staff Pictures (Box 37.1)
- UNITE Staff Pictures (Box 37.2)
- UNITE Staff Pictures (Box 37.3)
  - UNITE Staff Photographs (Box 37, Folder 1)
    3 CD-ROMs
- UNITE Global Pillage (Box 38)
  - UNITE Global Pillage - (Box 38, Folder 1)
    removed from box 3, ff9
- CINTAS/Star Bucks, Chicago, 5/14/2003 (Box 39)
  - CINTAS/Star Bucks, Chicago, 5/14/2003 - (Box 39, Folder 1)
- BOA/WGP, UNITE (Box 40)
  - BOA/WGP, UNITE - (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Adaptec - Easy CD Creator (Box 41)
  - Adaptec - Easy CD Creator -- (Box 41, Folder 1)
    pulled from box 10/ff7
- CD Creator 5.0 Platinum and upgrad 5.3 XP Patch (copy) (Box 42)
  - CD Creator 5.0 Platinum and upgrad 5.3 XP Patch (copy) -- (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn; Chinese New York (Box 43)
  - Brooklyn; Chinese New York (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Photography by Steve Donisch (Box 44)
  - Photography by Steve Donisch (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Mobile County - Pulbic Workers (Box 45)
  - Mobile County - Pulbic Workers (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Liz Claiborne - 4/8/2003 -- 1546-1835; 1903-2184 (Box 46)
  - Liz Claiborne - 4/8/2003 -- 1546-1835; 1903-2184 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Min Matheson, Wyoming Valley ILGWU (Box 47)
  - Min Matheson, Wyoming Valley ILGWU -- (Box 47, Folder 1)
    pulled from box 10/ff17
- UNITE (Box 48)
  - UNITE -- (Box 48, Folder 1)
    pulled from box 10/ff25
- 1977 Stockholders Photographs (Box 49, Folder 1)
  46 photographs
- Miscellaneous Blechman Singles (May 1976 at RR & Slaterboro) (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Martin Luther King, Sr. (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Citizens Labor Committee (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Feb. SJ Photographs (Box 49, Folder 5)
- March SJ Photos (Box 49, Folder 6)
- April SJ Photographs (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Times Square Demo 1/25/1977 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- NY CLUW Rally - Herald Sq. (Bobbie Hoff) (Box 49, Folder 9)
  21 photographs; news clippings
- Students at JPS Tower 8/11/1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Statesboro "Closed" (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Cleveland JPS Leafleting (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Minneapolis Leafleting (Box 49, Folder 13)
- O.O.T. "Testimony Premiers" (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Indianapolis, Kansas City Leafleting (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Shots for "Testimony" (Box 49, Folder 16)
- 1976 Stockholders Mtg (OLD) (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Mac Neil/Lehrer (Box 49, Folder 18)
- JPSEEC Pickets in NY 3/1/1977 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens Photographs - Miscellaneous (Box 50, Folder 1)
- JP Stevens (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Carolina Press Conference (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Pat Sullivan and Bill Jarman (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Clothing Industry (Cutters) (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Day Care (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Day Care Story (5/1978) (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Drummondville Strike - 1962 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Dubinsky, David (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Dominigan Rep/EM (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Education - EM (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Ellis Island (Box 51, Folder 8)
- NYJB - ESL Classes (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Cookbook/FACES - Labor Unity Winners (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Fall River Co. (Box 51, Folder 11)
  5 photographss
- Fieldcrest/Cannon (Box 51, Folder 12)
  8 photographss
- Fighting Health Inflation (Story) (Box 51, Folder 13)
  2 photographss
- Finkelstein, Esther (Box 51, Folder 14)
- FOAMADE (Box 51, Folder 15)
  78 photographss
- Frumin, Eric (Box 51, Folder 16)
  4 photographss
- Garden State Tanning (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Garment Corp. of America (ALA) (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Georgia, Tennessee, Alabama Joint Board - Spotlight -- 7/1978 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  13 photographss
- GRETF Demos Etc. 1993 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  12 photographss
- Guitar Company Guild - 1985 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  14 photographss
- Haiti Demo - Washington, DC 11/1992 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Haiti (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Hathaway Maine (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Hay Market (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Headwear Division (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Hill, Joe (Box 51, Folder 27)
- History - Celebrations, Demos, etc. (Box 51, Folder 28)
  11 photographss
- Local 1158 - Levis - Strauss, San Antonio, TX (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Local 1885 - Masland Carpets, Toronto (Box 51, Folder 30)
  6 photographss
- Local 2379 - Sileofab - Guelph, Ont. -- Picket Line Violence (Box 51, Folder 31)
  18 photographss
- Organizing (Box 51, Folder 32)
  20 photographss
- Organizing CF 1994 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- OSHA (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Passaic Strike (1926) (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Pendleton Woolen Mills (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia/Hillman Clinic 1994 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Phoenix Glove Co. (Andrews, S.C.) (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Pickets (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Picketlines (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Union label Boycotts - Picketing (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Pittston/Demos, Strikes, etc. (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Political Action - 1980 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Political Action 1981 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- RELTOC (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Poverty (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Retail Salesmen Story (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Puerto Rico - Union Campaigns (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Walter Reuther (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Roberts, John (Box 52, Folder 18)
  6 photograph
- Rocky Mountain Joint Board (Spotlight Story) (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Eleanor Roosevelt (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Scalamandre Silks (Box 52, Folder 21)
- Textile Leather (Box 53, Folder 1)
- This is ACTWU - How Union Works (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Time Clocks (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Toronto Joint Board (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Umbrellas (Historical) (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 6)
- White Tower/Detroit (Box 53, Folder 7)
- The Working American (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Yale Co-Op (Box 53, Folder 9)
- July/Aug 1990 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- JUSTICE/Sept. 1989 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- FUTURES (Box 53, Folder 12)
- L-89-22-1 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 14)
  news clippings
- Graphics (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Graphics Monthly Svc. (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Hispanic LCLAA/Labor files (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Demonstration Nat'l. Convention -- 7/1992; Photographer: Donna Binder/Impact visuals (Box 53, Folder 18)
- CLUW Convention - Seattle Oct. 1988 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Chinatown Demo - Tiananmen Square Protest (Box 53, Folder 20)
- S.F. Quake/hurricane Hugo/Catastrophes (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Asian Labor Festival (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Union meetings (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Contract negotiations (Box 54, Folder 2)
  100 photographs
- Linda Eber's, Kitty Dukakis pics (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Dukakis Photos (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Kitty Dukakis visits ILG Shop 8/1988; Abe Shrader's Shop, Locals 89-22-1, 10 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Cory Aquino at U.N. (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Eastern Airlines Strike (Box 54, Folder 7)
- David Dinkins (Box 54, Folder 8)
  60 photographs
- Domsey (Box 54, Folder 9)